Drew Allbritten Papers
Drew Allbritten Papers
- Georgia Association of Educators (GAE)
  - Meetings
    - 2001
      - Board of Directors, 9 Mar 2001 (Box 5)
      - Executive Committee, 9 Mar 2001 (Box 5)
      - Board of Directors, 27 Apr 2001 (Box 5)
      - Executive Committee, 27 Apr 2001 (Box 5)
      - Executive Committee, 18 Jun 2001 (Box 5)
      - Board of Directors, 19 Jun 2001 (Box 5)
      - State Caucus, 6 Jul 2001 (Box 5)
      - Board of Directors, 19 Jul 2001 (Box 5)
      - Executive Committee, 19 Jul 2001 (Box 5)
      - Executive Committee, 19-21 Sep 2001; 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Board of Directors, 21 Sep 2001; 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Executive Committee, 28 Oct 2001 (Box 5)
      - Executive Committee, 9 Nov 2001 (Box 5)
      - Representative Assembly, 10 Nov 2001 (Box 5)
      - Board of Directors, 27 Nov 2001 (Box 5)
      - Board of Directors, 1 Dec 2001; 2 folders (Box 6)
      - Executive Committee, 14 Dec 2001 (Box 6)
    - 2002
      - Executive Committee, 8 Jan 2002 (Box 6)
      - Board of Directors, 25 Jan 2002 (Box 6)
      - Executive Committee, 23 Feb 2002 (Box 6)
      - Board of Directors, 8 Mar 2002 (Box 6)
      - Executive Committee, 8 Mar 2002 (Box 6)
      - Board of Directors, 26 Apr 2002 (Box 6)
      - Executive Committee, 26 Apr 2002 (Box 6)
      - Executive Committee, 17 Jun 2002 (Box 6)
      - Board of Directors, 18 Jun 2002 (Box 6)
      - State Caucus, 30 Jun 2002 (Box 6)
      - Executive Committee, 8 Jul 2002 (Box 6)
      - Board of Directors, 10 Jul 2002 (Box 6)
  - Writings
    - Miscellaneous, by Allbritten, 1989-2001; articles, introductions, remarks, speeches, and notes; includes notes for speech on World Trade Center attacks (9/11/01) (Box 6)
  - Miscellany
    - Clippings, photograph, booklet "Restructuring Georgia's Schools," other assorted material (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous material, 2 folders (Box 6)
      See also General: Memorabilia: Miscellany (Box 1); General: Memorabilia: Photographs (Box 1)
- Council for Exceptional Children (CEC)
  - Correspondence-subject files
    - Annual conference, 2005 (Box 6)
    - Annual report, 2002 (Box 6)
    - Board of Directors handbook inserts, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Canadian CEC organizations, 2003 (Box 6)
    - "Celebrate Our Rising Stars", 2004; Allbritten was one of the presenters (Box 6)
    - Children and Youth Action Network (CAN), 2003-2004 (Box 6)
    - "Conversation Pieces", 2003; includes transcript of entire meeting (Box 6)
    - CEC Policy Manual, 2003; 2004; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Directories, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Evaluation and surveys, 2003; 2005 (Box 6)
    - Executive director job application, 2003; extremely detailed, includes presentation, SWOT assessment, more (Box 6)
    - Executive director keynote speech, 2005 (Box 15)
    - Invitations, 2002-2005 (Box 6)
    - National Center on Student Progress Monitoring, 2004-2005 (Box 6)
    - National convention, 2005 (Box 6)
    - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education (NCATE), 2004-2005 (Box 6)
    - Past president certificates, 2004 (Box 6)
    - Representative Assembly handbook, 2002-2004 (Box 6)
    - Roark, Karen Crow, 2004; 2005 (Box 6)
    - Staff meetings
      - Administrative staff, 2003-2005 (Box 6)
      - Miscellaneous, 2003-2005 (Box 7)
    - "Volunteerism in the U.S.", 2004; Allbritten was keynote speaker (Box 7)
    - Yes I Can! Foundation, 2001-2005; Allbritten was on Board of Directors (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence
      - External, 2002-2005 (Box 7)
      - Internal, 2003-2004 (Box 7)
  - Meetings
    - 2003
      - Board of Directors, 8-9 Apr 2003; 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Past Presidents Forum, 6 Sep 2003 (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 19 Sep 2003; 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Finance and Operations Committee, 31 Oct 2003 (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 25 Nov 2003 (Box 7)
    - 2004
      - Board of Directors, 23 Jan 2004 (Box 7)
      - Division Update, 20 Feb 2004 (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 25 Feb 2004 (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 31 Mar 2004 (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 14 Apr 2004 (Box 7)
      - Executive Directors, 11 Apr 2004 (Box 7)
      - Representative Assembly, 17 Apr 2004 (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 27 May 2004 (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 15 Jul 2004 (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 13 Sep 2004 (Box 7)
      - Finance and Audit Committee, 10 Sep 2004 (Box 7)
      - Past Presidents Forum, 18 Sep 2004 (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 1 Oct 2004; 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 8 Nov 2004 (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 13-15 Dec 2004; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - 2005
      - Board of Directors, 8 Jan 2005 (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 7 Mar 2005 (Box 7)
      - Board of Directors, 5 Apr 2005; 2 folders (Box 7)
      - Interdivisional Caucus, 5 Apr 2005 (Box 7)
      - Representative Assembly, 8 Apr 2005 (Box 8)
      - Board of Directors, 2 May 2005 (Box 8)
      - Board of Directors, 11 Jul 2005 (Box 8)
      - Board of Directors, 12 Sep 2005 (Box 8)
      - Past Presidents Forum, 17 Sep 2005 (Box 8)
      - Board of Directors, 30 Sep 2005; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Writings
    - Miscellaneous, by Allbritten, 2004-2005; Allbritten's articles, speeches, reports (Box 8)
  - Miscellany
    - Handwritten notes on range of topics, 2003-2005; 2 folders (Box 8)
      See also General: Awards and recognition (Box 1); General: Memorabilia: Miscellany (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous, notes, presentation, time sheets, CEC directory, other items (Box 15)